Guide to the Stages Theater records, 1978-2017 MS 740
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Administration and Board records (boxes 13-25), 1978-2017
  - Facilities, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Food Donations, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Gala Attendees, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Stages School, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 1996-01 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Review of Board Members, 1996-01 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Board Correspondence - Chairman John Leager, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Stages Theater Long-Range Planning Committee [Water-damaged], 1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Capital Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Capital Improvements of Technical Facilities, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Nonprofit Organizations, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Stages Impresarios, lists & correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Impresarios, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Site Description, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Foundations, 1996-2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - StageLight proposal, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Stages - Purpose & Activities, 1996-08-22 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Scene Shop Fire insurance documents, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Texas Playwrights' Festival, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Parking, 1996-1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Artistic Director Search Committee, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Critical Response Season 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Express Theatre Summer Camp, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Nominating Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Business Volunteers for the Arts, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Theater District Association, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Theater District, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Theater District, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Theater District Association correspondence & minutes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Managing Director, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Marketing Expanses, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Volunteer Management, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Young Audience of Houston Agreement, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Brochure Information, 1996-2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Board Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee minutes, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Impresarios, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Impresarios, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sponsorship Opportunities, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Marketing Program, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - United Way Management & Gifts-in-kind, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Building & Grounds Committee, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Building Dedication, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Procedures Manual, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Friends of the Board, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Houston Composers Alliance rental, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Joan Joanston Tribute Fund, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Marketing Committee, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Pierpoint Communications, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Voices from Theresienstudt, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Wall of Remembrance - AIDS Memorial, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - WineFest, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Greater Houston Partnership, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Board Handbook, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Long Range Planning / Education Group, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Impresarios, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Co-Production Policy, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Corporate Prospects, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Education Program Info, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Financial Planning, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Foundation Trustee Report, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Gifts-in-Kind Program, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Infernal Bridegroom Artist Residency Program, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - NSFRE, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Pension Plan, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Rice University MBA Project, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Tiffany & Co., 1998 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - 20th Anniversary Gala, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - WineFest, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Advisory Board, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Southwest Festival of New Plays, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Douglas Mitchell Play Festival, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Nominating Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Operating Budget, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder f)
  - Society of Stage Directors/Choreography, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Attendance, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Board Matrix, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Impresarios, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Board Retreat, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Donald Hightower Correspondence, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Stages Institutional Evaluation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Houston International Festival, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston/Harris County Neighborhood Arts Program Panel Review Book, October, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Human Resources Manual Meetings, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Internships, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Puppet Theater, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Special Events Committee, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Early Stages Houston Institute for Cultural Studies, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Full Gallop Benefit (Tootsies), 1999 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Jewish Community Center, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Kingswood College, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Strand Theatre, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Texas Accountants & Lawyers for the Arts, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - WineFest, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Work Study Program, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Intensive Services Program Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Staff Meetings, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Beeson Properties, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors Policies and Procedures, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Board Committee Positions, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Board Letter Acceptance, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Board Policy & Procedures Manual, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Business Plan, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - By-Laws as Amended, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Grant Proposals, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Leadership Houston Arts Day, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Pat Berner Correspondence, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Managing Director Thomas Smith Correspondence, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Roasting Lynn Ashby, May 4, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Shakespeare Outreach program, University of Houston, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Susie Bowers Memorial Gifts, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Impresarios, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Marketing Plan, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Parking Issues, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Season Sales, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Southwest Festival of New Plays, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Staff Meeting, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Woodway Financial Advisors, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Board Minutes & Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Goals, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - God's Man in Texas, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Season Comped Tickets, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Budget revisions, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Artistic Director Rob Bundy Correspondence, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Recommendations for a Houston Theater Alliance, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Finance Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Human Festival, 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Annual Fund, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - By-laws as amended, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Managing Director Ken McLaughlin correspondence, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Foundation Prospects, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Heart of Woman - legal, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta charity donations, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Marketing Committee, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Name change to John & Jean Yeager Theater, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - NEA Grant Application, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Performance Calendar, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Production Agreements, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Runt of the Litter, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Writer's Market, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Actor's Equity Association, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Alley Theater, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Austin Playfest, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Board Meetings, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Building the Board, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - City of Houston, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Cultural Arts Coalition of Houston / Harris Co., 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Development Goals, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Executive Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Finance Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - House Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Impresarios, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Performance Sales reports, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Planning Retreat, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Production Budget Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Reviews, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Single ticket goals, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Staff evaluation forms by role (blank), 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - TCG Pilot Project, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Theatre Communications Group, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Year-end fundraising appeal, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Fondren Foundation notes, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - The Laramie Project education program, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - R* Ushers Agreement, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Audit, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - The Big Voice, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Budgets, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Budget Revisions, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - City of Houston, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Giving, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County grant application packet, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Department Heads, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Impresarios, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Individual giving, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Internship program, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Job Descriptions, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Marketing Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Meadows Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Production Contracts, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Year-end Fundraising Campaign, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Production Expenses (1/2), 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Production Expenses, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Strategic Planning [Water Damage], 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Impresario Catering, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Leader's Circle Meetings, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Nonprofit Listening Post Project, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Special Events History, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Board List, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Cash Flow, Summer 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - City of Houston, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Department Head Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Executive Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Houston Endowment Matching Gift, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Impresario Donations, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Production Budgets, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Single Donations, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Special Events Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Sponsorship Packets, 2003-2004 Season (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Staff Meeting Materials, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Writers in the School, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Mini Cooper raffle, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Nominating Committee, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Always...Patsy Cline budgets, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Financial Balance sheets, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Foundations' Board Member Lists, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Operation 170 (Fundraising), 2004 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Pan American Cultural Exchange, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Board Retreat, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Board Handbook, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Board Meetings, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Box Office Recap, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - City of Houston correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Department heads, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Market Research materials, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Production Issues, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Staff Meetings, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Stages - Hobby Center, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Development / Strategic Plan, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Grant - Houston Endowment, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - National Arts Strategies & Stanford Graduate School of Business leadership program, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Turak, French puppet show logistics, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Young Actors Conservatory, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Board / Staff retreat, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Department Head Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Early Stages, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Foundation correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Impresarios roster, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Meadows Foundation, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Production Budgets, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Staff Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Planning, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Young Audiences Residencies, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Assistive Listening System, 2005-2007 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Board Meetings, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Budgets, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Young Actor's Conservatory, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Board handbook, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Board Meetings, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Department Head Meetings, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Development, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Gala Budget, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Board retreat, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Bylaws & Job Descriptions, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Department Head Meeting, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - HSPVA Advisory Board, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Shakespeare Outreach - UH, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Staff meetings, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Susan Smith Blackburn Prize, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Thank You letters for ticket donations, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Board Meetings, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Board orientation, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Deluxe Theater Project / 5th Ward, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Eclectica, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Executive Board Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Finance Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Production Budgets, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Production Notes & Budge, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Shunya Theater costs, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Staff Meetings, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Department Heads Meeting, 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - A Renaissance in the Classroom - CASE, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 2008-2009 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Season planning, 2008-2009 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Unbeatable / Pink Ribbons project fundraising & script, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Unbeatable / Pink Ribbons Projects correspondence & Nominations, 2008-2009 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Provocative propositions (planning), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Plan "Reach 2017", 2009-2012 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Budgets, 2009-2010 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Usher Lists / Sign-in Book, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements, 2011-2012 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Feasibility & Planning Study, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statements, 2012-2015 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Executive Meetings, 2013-2016 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Arts Access Initiative, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Development Meetings, 2014-2016 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Houston Endowment application, 2014-2015 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Brown Foundation, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Co-production Agreement Between Stages and Black Lab Theater, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Gala, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Producing Artistic Director McLaughlin, Kenn, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Society for Bioethics and Humanities - Notes, Fall 2015 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Texas Playwright Festival, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Lightning - Audio Supervisor, 2015-2016 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Nominating Committee & Governance, 2015-2016 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Strategic Planning, 2015-2016 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Allen Parkway Arts Center Board Meeting, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Budget, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Gala, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Miller Outdoor Theater Program Committee funding application, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Capital Campaign committee, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - New Play development & licensing program, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Staff Meetings, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors meeting, 2016-2017 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Board Survey, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Undated Correspondence, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Employee policy for outside work, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Performance Evaluation template, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Seating Plans, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Awards, 1997-2001 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Series III: Development (boxes 26-30 - restricted), 1981-2004
  - Abell-Hanger Foundation, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Actor's Equity, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - AIM Foundation, 2001-2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Air Liquide America, 1980-2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Albert & Margaret Alkek Foundation, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Alley Theater, 1984-1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Anchorage Foundation of Texas, 1993-2002 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - M.D. Anderson Foundation, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Edward H. Andrews Foundation, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Arts Partners, 1990-1997 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - ASSITEJ, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Baker and Botts, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Barrow Foundation, 1992-2001 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Bayou Charitable Trust, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - The Bayou Fund, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - The Bernard Foundation, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Benefits to Supporters, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Cameron Foundation, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Sarah Campbell Blaffer Foundation, 1989-2004 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Board List, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Dr. Edith F. Bondi Foundation, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - BP, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - The Brown Foundation, 1982-1994 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - The Brown Foundation, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - The Brown Foundation, 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Barbara Bush Foundation for Family Literacy, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Gordon and Mary Cain Foundation, 1990-2001 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Cain Foundation, 1988-1995 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Children's Museum, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - The Clayton Fund, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Clift Foundation, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Cockrell Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Coneway Family Foundation, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Conference Travel, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Cooper Industries Foundation, 2001-2004 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Cullen Foundation, 1985-2003 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 1996-1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 1998-2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County - Intensive Services Program, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County - Leader's Circle, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston - Stabilization Enterprise, 1992-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston / Harris County - Touring, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Development Committee, 1988-1996 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Development Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Donation Info, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Donor Prospects, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Duddleston Foundation, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - The Lillian & C.W. Duncan Foundation, 1990-2004 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Education Program, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Elkins Foundation, 1990-2002 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - El Paso Corporate Foundation, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Enron Foundation, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Williams Stamps Farish Fund, 1984-1999 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Favrot Foundation, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Finger Foundation, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Ray C. Fish Foundation, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Fondren Foundation, 1986-1997 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Ford Foundation, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Foundation Requests, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Friedkin Foundation, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Frill Foundation, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Fringe Quarter Cultural Council Meeting, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Fund for New American Plays, 1987-1990 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - George Foundation, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Gilman Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Melbern and Susanne M. Glasscock Foundation, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Key Personnel, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Gregory Charitable Trust, 1987-1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - GRITS Foundation, 1998-2003 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - George and Mary Josephine Hammon Foundation, 1982-1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Jacob and Terese Hershey Foundation, 1984-1990 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Albert and Ethel Herzstein Charitable Fund, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Hobby Family Foundation, 1982-1995 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Hollyfield Foundation, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Horlock Foundation, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Houston Arts Fund, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Houston Endowment, 1988-2000 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - HISD - Business Development, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Houston Industries Inc. Foundation, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Huffington Foundation, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Humana, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Humphreys Foundation, 1981-2000 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - In-Kind Donations, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Joe Jamail Foundation, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Junior League of Houston, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 22)